Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files K-O, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files M
    - Morris, Leander (Box A-86, Folder 242)
    - Morris, Lenwood (Box A-86, Folder 243)
    - Morris, Leonard (Box A-86, Folder 244)
    - Morris, Leo A. (Box A-86, Folder 245)
    - Morris, Leslie (Box A-86, Folder 246)
    - Morris, Linwood (Box A-86, Folder 247)
    - Morris, Maud (Box A-86, Folder 248)
    - Morris, Newbold (Box A-86, Folder 249)
    - Morris, Phoebe (Box A-86, Folder 250)
    - Morris, Polly (Box A-86, Folder 251)
    - Morris, Reginald O. (Dr.) (Box A-86, Folder 252)
    - Morris, Ruth (Box A-86, Folder 253)
      Photographer if identified: Ann Meuer
    - Morris, Robert E. (Box A-86, Folder 254)
    - Rev. Robert Morris (Box A-86, Folder 255)
    - Morris, Ruby (Box A-86, Folder 256)
    - Morris, Samuel (Box A-86, Folder 257)
    - Morris, Sharon (Box A-86, Folder 258)
    - Morris, Solomon Jr. (Box A-86, Folder 259)
      Photographer if identified: Monroe S. Frederick
    - Morris, Stella (Box A-86, Folder 260)
    - Morris, Thomas E. (Box A-86, Folder 261)
    - Morris, Toni-Lou (Box A-86, Folder 262)
    - Morris, W. D. (Box A-86, Folder 263)
    - Morris, Wm. R. (Box A-86, Folder 264)
    - Zandra Morris (Box A-86, Folder 265)
    - Morrisania Neighborhood Family Care Center (Box A-86, Folder 266)
      Photographer if identified: Robert Reilly
    - Morrisey, Alex (Box A-86, Folder 267)
    - Morrishow, Stacey (Box A-86, Folder 268)
    - Morrison, Alan (Box A-86, Folder 269)
    - Douglass Morrison (Box A-86, Folder 270)
    - Morrison, Dorothy (Box A-86, Folder 271)
    - Morrison, Elihu Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-86, Folder 272)
    - Morrison, Eugene (Box A-86, Folder 273)
    - Morrison, Jesse (Box A-87, Folder 1)
      One print has staples through image.
    - Morrison, John (Box A-87, Folder 2)
    - Morrison, Mamon (Box A-87, Folder 3)
      Photographer if identified: James W. B. Burke
    - Morrison, Mildred (Box A-87, Folder 4)
    - Morrison, Paul J. (Rev.) (Box A-87, Folder 5)
    - Morrison, Paerle G. (Dr.) (Box A-87, Folder 6)
    - Morrison, Thomas J., Sr. (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-87, Folder 7)
      Photographer if identified: Ringgold
    - Morrison, Toni (Box A-87, Folder 8)
      Also six velox prints. One print has typescript press release (two leaves) attached with paperclip.
    - Morrison, Michele Trudi (Box A-87, Folder 9)
      Photographer if identified: Official Photograph The White House
    - Morrow, Charles (Box A-87, Folder 10)
    - Morrow, E. Fred (Box A-87, Folder 11)
    - Morrow, Ed (Box A-87, Folder 12)
    - Morrow, Frederick (Mrs). (Box A-87, Folder 13)
    - Morrow, E. Frederick (Box A-87, Folder 14)
    - Morrow, James S. (Box A-87, Folder 15)
    - Morrow, Monroe (Box A-87, Folder 16)
    - Morrow, Roy (Box A-87, Folder 17)
    - Morrow, Willie L. (Box A-87, Folder 18)
    - Morse, Edward, (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-87, Folder 19)
      Photographer if identified: Paramount Photographers
    - Morse, George (Box A-87, Folder 20)
    - Morse, Norman (Box A-87, Folder 21)
    - Morsell, Fred (Box A-87, Folder 22)
    - Morsell, John A. (Box A-87, Folder 23)
      Note on folder: "See: Inactive file."
    - Morsell, John A. (Mrs.) (Box A-87, Folder 24)
    - Morson, Elihu H. (Box A-87, Folder 25)
    - Mortel, Rodrigue (Dr.) (Box A-87, Folder 26)
    - Morten, Baker E. (Box A-87, Folder 27)
    - Morten, George E. (Box A-87, Folder 28)
    - Morton, Azie (Box A-87, Folder 29)
    - Morton, Annette (Box A-87, Folder 30)
    - Morton, Azie T. (Mrs.) (Box A-87, Folder 31)
    - Morton, Belinda (Box A-87, Folder 32)
    - Morton, Franklin W. Jr. (Justice) (Box A-87, Folder 33)
    - Morton, Gerald (Box A-87, Folder 34)
    - Morton, Hosea (Box A-87, Folder 35)
    - Morton, Joe (Box A-87, Folder 36)
    - Morton, Sherill (Box A-87, Folder 37)
    - Mosby, Jerry (Rev.) (Box A-87, Folder 38)
    - Mosby, Olga (Box A-87, Folder 39)
    - Moseby, John (Box A-87, Folder 40)
    - Moseley, Albert (Box A-87, Folder 41)
    - Moseley, Anthony D. (Box A-87, Folder 42)
    - Mosley, Calvin E. Jr. (Box A-87, Folder 43)
    - Moseley, Julius Dr. (Box A-87, Folder 44)
    - Mosely, Leavin (Dr. & Son) (Box A-87, Folder 45)
    - Mosely, Robert (Box A-87, Folder 46)
    - Moses, Gilbert (Box A-87, Folder 47)
    - Moses, Kenneth (Box A-87, Folder 48)
    - Moses, Knolly (Box A-87, Folder 49)
    - Moses, Robert (Box A-87, Folder 50)
    - Moses, Sybil (Mrs.) (Box A-87, Folder 51)
      Photographer if identified: Francis C. Ward Inc.,
    - Moses, Yolanda T. (Box A-87, Folder 52)
    - Moshette, Denise (Box A-87, Folder 53)
    - Mosler, John (Box A-87, Folder 54)
      One print has newspaper clipping adhered on verso; two have single-leaf press releases attached.
      Photographer if identified: News Voice International, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Mosler, Sheila (Box A-87, Folder 55)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, David Norman
    - Mosley, Bob (Box A-87, Folder 56)
    - Mosley Brothers, The (Box A-87, Folder 57)
    - Mosley, Corrine (Box A-87, Folder 58)
    - Mosley, Daniel (Box A-87, Folder 59)
    - Mosley, Edward (Box A-87, Folder 60)
    - Mosley, George E. (Box A-87, Folder 61)
    - Mosley, John E. (Dr.) (Box A-87, Folder 62)
      Note on folder: "See folder: Association for Sickle Cell Anemia."
    - Mosley, Joseph (Box A-87, Folder 63)
    - Mosley, Robert (Box A-87, Folder 64)
    - Mosley, Roger (Box A-87, Folder 65)
    - Moseley, Renee (Box A-87, Folder 66)
    - Moseley, Ron (Box A-87, Folder 67)
    - Mosely, Sarah (Box A-87, Folder 68)
    - Mosely, Carlos (Box A-87, Folder 69)
    - Mosely, Daniel (Box A-87, Folder 70)
    - Mosely, Joseph (Dr.) (Box A-87, Folder 71)
    - Mosely, Rhonda (Box A-87, Folder 72)
    - Mosely, Robert (Box A-87, Folder 73)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Mosely, Sylvester (Box A-87, Folder 74)
    - "Moses" (Box A-87, Folder 75)
    - Moses, Edwin (Box A-87, Folder 76)
    - Moses Sisters (Box A-87, Folder 77)
    - Moses, John W. (Dr. Rev.) (Box A-87, Folder 78)
    - Moses, Birdena, S. (Box A-87, Folder 79)
    - Moshariki, Job (Box A-87, Folder 80)
    - Mosely, B. J. (Box A-87, Folder 81)
    - Mosley, Elwood (Box A-87, Folder 82)
    - Mosley, Roger (Box A-87, Folder 83)
    - Mosley, Snub (Box A-87, Folder 84)
    - Mosley, Walter (Box A-87, Folder 85)
    - Moss, Elizabeth Murphy Phillips Moss (Mrs.) (Box A-87, Folder 86)
    - Moss, Ellen Frances (Miss) (Box A-87, Folder 87)
    - Moss, Joy (Box A-87, Folder 88)
    - Moss, Louise Kemp (Box A-87, Folder 89)
    - Moss, Lucia Zynn (Box A-87, Folder 90)
      One photocopy of a print.
    - Moss, Otis Rev. (Jr.) (Box A-87, Folder 91)
    - Moss, Robert (Box A-87, Folder 92)
    - Moss, Ron (Box A-87, Folder 93)
    - Moss, William H. (Box A-87, Folder 94)
    - Mossman, LaVern (Box A-87, Folder 95)
    - Mota, Manny (Box A-87, Folder 96)
    - Mother Ame Zion Church (Box A-87, Folder 97)
    - Mother Night (Box A-87, Folder 98)
      Single-leaf press release.
    - Mother Walls Ame Zion Church (Box A-87, Folder 99)
      Eight prints are stuck together.
    - Mother's Day (Box A-87, Folder 100)
    - Motley, Constance (Box A-87, Folder 101)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, Whitestone Photo, Gill Photographers, Tex Harris, James W. B. Burke, Cecil Layne, James Gilbert, Bill Anderson, Ed Bagwell
    - Motley, Constance (Box A-87, Folder 102)
      Photographer if identified: Whitestone Photo, Ed Bagwell, Wagner International Photos, United Press International Photo, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Motley, John (Box A-87, Folder 103)
      Photographer if identified: Official Photograph/Board of Education City of New York
    - Motley, Philip (Box A-87, Folder 104)
      Also one velox print and one photocopy on blue paper.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, KJS Collection
    - Mott Haven Church (Box A-87, Folder 105)
    - Motley, Ernest (D.) (Box A-87, Folder 106)
    - Motley, Susan (Box A-87, Folder 107)
    - Motley, Wendell (Box A-87, Folder 108)
    - Morton, Azie (Box A-87, Folder 109)
    - Motown Record Company (Box A-87, Folder 110)
      Two prints have single typescript leaf press releases attached.
    - Mott, Minnie (Box A-87, Folder 111)
    - Motz, Cassandra Mason (Box A-87, Folder 112)
    - Mouchette, Edward D. (Rev.) (Box A-87, Folder 113)
    - Moultrice, H. Carl (Box A-87, Folder 114)
      Photographer if identified: Chase Ltd.
    - Mouthrie, Willa (Singers) (Box A-87, Folder 115)
    - Moultrie, William (Box A-87, Folder 116)
    - Moun, Joseph (Box A-87, Folder 117)
    - Motley, Marian (Box A-87, Folder 118)
    - Mount Carmel (Box A-87, Folder 119)
      Photographer if identified: Dave Green Photo
    - Mount Morris Everyman Theatre (Box A-87, Folder 120)
    - Mt. Morris Park Hosp. (Box A-87, Folder 121)
    - Mount Morris Park (Box A-87, Folder 122)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Bro. David McAdams
    - Mt. Nebo Baptist Church Choir (Box A-87, Folder 123)
    - Ms. Charisma (Box A-87, Folder 124)
    - Mt. Zion Baptist Church (Box A-87, Folder 125)
    - Mounties (Box A-87, Folder 126)
    - Mouzon, Alphonse (Box A-87, Folder 127)
    - MOVE (Box A-87, Folder 128)
    - Move Philadelphia (Box A-87, Folder 129)
    - Movies (Billings) (Box A-87, Folder 130)
      Photographer if identified: Diener, Hauser, Bates
    - Movie (Billings) (Box A-87, Folder 131)
    - Moye, Eugene (Box A-87, Folder 132)
      One print has staple in border.
    - Moye, Lemuel A., III (Mrs.) (Box A-87, Folder 133)
    - Moyer, Bill (Box A-87, Folder 134)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P. (Box A-87, Folder 135)
      Two prints have typescript press releases (five leaves) attached with paperclip; one has single-leaf press release attached on verso.
    - Mozambique (Box A-87, Folder 136)
      Also one computer-printed leaf and one photocopied leaf loose in folder (Images of maps).
    - Mozie, Eddie Jr. (Box A-87, Folder 137)
    - Mtambanenque, S. U. (Box A-87, Folder 138)
    - Mtume (Box A-87, Folder 139)
    - Mtume (Box A-87, Folder 140)
    - Mubi, Simomo (Box A-87, Folder 141)
    - Muckle, Ernest A. (Box A-87, Folder 142)
      Print is adhered to cardstock.
    - Mueller, Betty (Box A-87, Folder 143)
    - Mugabe, Robert (Box A-87, Folder 144)
      Also two computer-printed leaves loose in folder (one graphic image and one photograph).
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, The White House
    - Mugabe, Sally (Box A-87, Folder 145)
    - Muganero, Francis L. (Bishop) (Box A-87, Folder 146)
      Photographer if identified: Herbert Newlin, Bill Mitchell, Routel Studio
    - Muhammed, Amibar (Box A-87, Folder 147)
    - Muhammed, Balozi Zayd (Box A-87, Folder 148)
    - Muhammed, Hussan (Box A-87, Folder 149)
    - Muhammed, Idris (Box A-87, Folder 150)
    - Muhammed, James (Box A-87, Folder 151)
    - Muhammed, Elijah (Box A-87, Folder 152)
      One print is torn/damaged; two are stuck together. Also four velox prints (three of which are stuck together).
      Photographer if identified: Merrill A. Roberts, Wide World Photos, Merrill Roberts, Burley Photography
    - Muhammed, Wallace (Box A-87, Folder 153)
      Stapled typescript press release (four leaves). Also four velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene Photo, United Press International Photo, Frank James,
    - Muhammed, Min. Khalid Abdul (Nation Of Islam) (Box A-87, Folder 154)
    - Muhammed, Mustafa (Box A-87, Folder 155)
      Photographer if identified: Jenny Martin
    - Muhammad, Sanoria X Hayes (Box A-87, Folder 156)
    - Muhammed, Shadujah (Box A-87, Folder 157)
      Photographer if identified: Gill Photographers, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Muhammed Univ. (Box A-87, Folder 158)
    - Muhammad, Murad (Box A-87, Folder 159)
    - Muhammad, Vergie R. (Sister) (Box A-87, Folder 160)
    - Muahmmad, Vernell (Box A-87, Folder 161)
    - Muir, Henry (Rev.) (Box A-87, Folder 162)
      Photographer if identified: Spectrum Photo Studio
    - Muka Dehn Jazz Dance Theatre (Box A-87, Folder 163)
      Photographer if identified: Peter Moore
    - Muktananda, Baba (Box A-87, Folder 164)
      One print has typescript press release (six leaves) attached with paperclip.
    - Muley, Elba (Box A-87, Folder 165)
    - Mulikita, F. M. (Box A-87, Folder 166)
    - Muller, Randy (Box A-87, Folder 167)
    - Mullet, Donald (Box A-87, Folder 168)
    - Mulligan, Gerry (Box A-87, Folder 169)
    - Mulligan, Gerry (Box A-87, Folder 170)
    - Mulligan, Jon (Box A-87, Folder 171)
      Note on folder: "See John Bece."
    - Mullings, Queen (Box A-87, Folder 172)
    - Mullins, Chris (Box A-87, Folder 173)
    - Mullins, Curtis (Box A-87, Folder 174)
    - Mulzac, Hugh (Capt.) (Box A-87, Folder 175)
    - Mulzac, Marcia (Box A-87, Folder 176)
      Photographer if identified: Badford Bachrach
    - Mulzac, Una J. I. (Rev.) (Box A-87, Folder 177)
    - Mumford, J.D. (Rev.) (Box A-87, Folder 178)
    - Mumford, Walter (Box A-87, Folder 179)
    - Mumphrey, Jerry (Box A-87, Folder 180)
    - Munce, Bernice (Box A-87, Folder 181)
    - Mundy, Eugene (Box A-87, Folder 182)
    - Mungin, Melvin A. (Box A-87, Folder 183)
      Photographer if identified: Photo by Hayes FI-1-1781
    - Munlin, Barbara Jean (Box A-87, Folder 184)
    - Munn, Joseph B., Jr. (Box A-87, Folder 185)
    - Munoz, Gloria Peter (Box A-87, Folder 186)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, Cecil Layne
    - Munoz-Marin, Louis (Box A-87, Folder 187)
      Note on folder: "Gov. of Puerto Rico." Print has single typescript leaf letter attached with paperclip.
    - Munroe, Loi (Box A-87, Folder 188)
    - Munroe, Sam + Scott (Box A-87, Folder 189)
    - Munroe, Trevor (Box A-87, Folder 190)
    - Mungi, Brig. Jonah (Box A-87, Folder 191)
      Photographer if identified: The Salvation Army
    - Murcer, Bobby (Box A-87, Folder 192)
    - Murchison, Murch (Box A-87, Folder 193)
      Print has single-leaf press release attached on verso.
    - Murdew, George (Box A-87, Folder 194)
    - Murdock, Gilbert (Box A-87, Folder 195)
      Photographer if identified: Larry Hicks
    - Murdock, Jackie Bebe (Box A-87, Folder 196)
    - Murg, Loorine (Box A-87, Folder 197)
    - Murial, Greg (Box A-87, Folder 198)
    - Murph, Essie O. (Mrs.) (Box A-87, Folder 199)
    - Murphy, Alexander (Box A-87, Folder 200)
    - Murphy, Anita E. (Mrs.) (Box A-87, Folder 201)
    - Murphy, Arlene (Box A-87, Folder 202)
    - Murphy, Arthur (Box A-87, Folder 203)
    - Murphy, Austin (Box A-87, Folder 204)
    - Murphy, Bryan (Box A-87, Folder 205)
    - Murphy, Calvin (Box A-87, Folder 206)
    - Murphy, Carl (Box A-87, Folder 207)
    - Murphy, Carmen (Box A-87, Folder 208)
    - Murphy, Charles (Box A-87, Folder 209)
      Photographer if identified: Emerich C. Gross
    - Murph, Chee Chee (Box A-87, Folder 210)
    - Murphy, Cicero (Box A-87, Folder 211)
      Photographer if identified: Handy-Boesser Photographers, George Jervas, Bro. David McAdams
    - Murphy, Claude (Mr. + Mrs.) (Box A-87, Folder 212)
    - Murphy, Cornelia (Box A-87, Folder 213)
    - Murphy, Daniel H. (Box A-87, Folder 214)
    - Murphy, Delores (Box A-87, Folder 215)
    - Murphy, Dorothy Patrick (Box A-87, Folder 216)
    - Murphy, Ernest (Box A-87, Folder 217)
    - Murphy, Eunice H. (Mrs.) (Box A-87, Folder 218)
    - Murphy, Francis T., Jr. (Judge) (Box A-87, Folder 219)
    - Murphy, Fred (Box A-87, Folder 220)
    - Murphy, Henry (Box A-87, Folder 221)
    - Murphy, Howard H. (Box A-87, Folder 222)
    - Murphy, James "Cicero" (Box A-87, Folder 223)
    - Murphy, Jo-Ann (Box A-87, Folder 224)
    - Murphy, John A. (Box A-87, Folder 225)
    - Murphy, John M. (Box A-87, Folder 226)
    - Murphy, Joseph P., Jr. (Box A-87, Folder 227)
    - Murphy, Joseph Samson (Box A-87, Folder 228)
    - Murphy, Justine J. (Box A-87, Folder 229)
    - Murphy, Kenneth (Box A-87, Folder 230)
    - Murphy, Lawrence (Box A-87, Folder 231)
    - Murphy, Lillian (Box A-87, Folder 232)
    - Murphy, Lillie (Box A-87, Folder 233)
    - Murphy, Lisa (Box A-87, Folder 234)
    - Murphy, Lois A. (Box A-87, Folder 235)
    - Murphy, Michael (Box A-87, Folder 236)
    - Murphy, Miriam (Box A-87, Folder 237)
    - Murphy, Patrick (Box A-87, Folder 238)
      Note on folder: "Police Comm." Also one velox print. One print has typescript press release (two leaves) attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, King Photographers, Dave Greene Creative Photo Service Inc.
    - Murphy, Pickles (Box A-87, Folder 239)
    - Murphy, Quinn W. (Box A-87, Folder 240)
      Photographer if identified: Markow Photography
    - Murphy, Reg. (Box A-87, Folder 241)
    - Murphy, Rita (Box A-87, Folder 242)
      Photographer if identified: Van Picture Service Inc.
    - Murphy, Robert (Sgt.) (Box A-87, Folder 243)
    - Murphy, Rose (Box A-87, Folder 244)
    - Murphy, Saac (Box A-87, Folder 245)
    - Murphy, Thomas A. (Box A-87, Folder 246)
    - Murphy, Thomas S. (Box A-87, Folder 247)
    - Murphy, William (Judge) (Box A-87, Folder 248)
    - Murrain, Edward "Sonny" (Box A-87, Folder 249)
    - Murray, Albert Jr. (Box A-87, Folder 250)
    - Murray, Albert R. (Box A-87, Folder 251)
    - Murray Alex J. (Box A-87, Folder 252)
    - Murray, Andrea (Box A-87, Folder 253)
    - Murray, Archibald R. (Box A-87, Folder 254)
    - Murray, Arthur (Box A-87, Folder 255)
    - Murray, Bonnie (Box A-87, Folder 256)
    - Murray, Carl (Box A-87, Folder 257)
      Also one typescript leaf attached.
    - Murray, Cahterine A. (Mrs.) (Box A-87, Folder 258)
    - Murray, Chales A. (Box A-87, Folder 259)
    - Murray, Chisholm (Box A-87, Folder 260)
    - Murray, Charles (Box A-87, Folder 261)
    - Murray, Clara (Box A-87, Folder 262)
    - Murray, David (Box A-87, Folder 263)
    - Murray, Deloris (Box A-87, Folder 264)
    - Murray, Derrick (Box A-87, Folder 265)
    - Murray, Dorothy (Box A-87, Folder 266)
    - Murray, Drew (Box A-87, Folder 267)
    - Murray, Earle D. (Box A-87, Folder 268)
      Photographer if identified: Crutchfield
    - Murray, Elaine D. (Box A-87, Folder 269)
    - Murphy, Lugwig (Box A-87, Folder 270)
      Photographer if identified: Monroe S. FrederickII
    - Murray, George (Box A-87, Folder 271)
    - Murray, George (Dr.) (Box A-87, Folder 272)
      Photographer if identified: E. McDonald
    - Murray, George H. (Rev.) (Box A-87, Folder 273)
    - Murray, Geoge J. A. (Box A-87, Folder 274)
    - Murray, George, Sr. (Box A-87, Folder 275)
    - Murray, Georgia L. (Box A-87, Folder 276)
    - Murray, Hapta J. (Box A-87, Folder 277)
    - Murray, Henry (Box A-87, Folder 278)
    - Murray, Herbert H. (Box A-87, Folder 279)
    - Murray, Herbert H. (Box A-87, Folder 280)
    - Murray, Jame (Box A-87, Folder 281)
    - Murray, James H. (Box A-87, Folder 282)
    - Murray, James P. (Box A-87, Folder 283)
    - Murray, Joan (Box A-87, Folder 284)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Tex Harris, M. Jaffe, A. Hansen Studio, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Ace Creative Photos
    - Murray, John (Box A-87, Folder 285)
      Photographer if identified: Jay Seymour, Wagner International Photos Inc.
    - Murray, Father John (Box A-87, Folder 286)
    - Murray, John F. Jr. (Mrs.) (Box A-87, Folder 287)
      Print has typescript press release (two leaves) attached.
      Photographer if identified: James Heffernan
    - Murray, Juggy (Box A-87, Folder 288)
    - Murray, June (Box A-87, Folder 289)
    - Murray, Keith (Mr. + Mrs.) (Box A-87, Folder 290)
    - Murray, Lester (Box A-87, Folder 291)
    - Murray, Lucy (Box A-87, Folder 292)
    - Murray, Marcy P. (Mrs.) (Box A-87, Folder 293)
    - Murray, Marlene (Box A-87, Folder 294)
      Folder notes "Miss Jamaica."
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Pan American World Airways
    - Murray, Michael (Box A-88, Folder 1)
      Print has one press release and one typescript leaf attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Maury Englander
    - Murray, Mickey (Box A-88, Folder 2)
    - Murray, Patricia (Box A-88, Folder 3)
    - Murray, Paul (Box A-88, Folder 4)
    - Murray, Pauli (Dr.) (Box A-88, Folder 5)
    - Murray, Pearl (Box A-88, Folder 6)
    - Murry, Peter Marshall (Dr. + Mrs.) (Box A-88, Folder 7)
      Photographer if identified: Ralph Mitchell, McAdams
    - Murray, Philip (Box A-88, Folder 8)
    - Murray, Rita D. (Box A-88, Folder 9)
    - Murray, Robert F. (Dr.) (Box A-88, Folder 10)
    - Murray, Robert F. (Dr.) (Box A-88, Folder 11)
    - Murray, Robin C. (Box A-88, Folder 12)
    - Murray, Rosalind (Box A-88, Folder 13)
    - Murray, Rufus (Box A-88, Folder 14)
    - Murray the K (Box A-88, Folder 15)
      One print has typescript note attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Dave Hollander
    - Murray, Tom (Box A-88, Folder 16)
      Contains large folded sheet with four images on it.
    - Murray, Walter I. (Dr.) (Box A-88, Folder 17)
      Photographer if identified: Maurice Lehv, Wilson, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Murray, Wendell C. (Box A-88, Folder 18)
    - Murray, William (Box A-88, Folder 19)
    - Murrell, Alroy (Box A-88, Folder 20)
    - Murrell, Alvin + Julia (Box A-88, Folder 21)
    - Murrell, Cameron (Box A-88, Folder 22)
    - Murrell, George (Mr. + Mrs.) (Box A-88, Folder 23)
    - Murrow, Barbara M. (Box A-88, Folder 24)
    - Murrow, Edward R. (Box A-88, Folder 25)
    - Murtha, John (Box A-88, Folder 26)
    - Murvin, Junior (Box A-88, Folder 27)
      Photographer if identified: Kim Gottlieb
    - Musasama, Sana (Box A-88, Folder 28)
    - Muse, Andrew C. (Box A-88, Folder 29)
    - Muse, Clarence (Box A-88, Folder 30)
      Note on folder: "(NAACP)."
    - Muse, Edwards (Box A-88, Folder 31)
    - Muse, Frankie (Box A-88, Folder 32)
    - Muse Museum (Box A-88, Folder 33)
    - Museka, Abbey Lincoln A. (Box A-88, Folder 34)
    - Museo El Barrio (Box A-88, Folder 35)
    - Museum (Box A-88, Folder 36)
    - Museum of Modern Art (Box A-88, Folder 37)
      Photographer if identified: Leonardo Le Grand, Frank J. Thomas
    - Museveni, Yoweri Kaguta (Box A-88, Folder 38)
    - Musgrave, Louis (Box A-88, Folder 39)
      Photographer if identified: Burley Photos
    - Musgrave, Louise (Box A-88, Folder 40)
      Photographer if identified: Vendel Nichols
    - Music + Art Basketball Team (Box A-88, Folder 41)
    - Music + Art High School (Box A-88, Folder 42)
      Photographer if identified: Big M Photo Service, Randy Waterman
    - Music Makers (Box A-88, Folder 43)
    - Musical Family (Box A-88, Folder 44)
    - Musical Menn (Box A-88, Folder 45)
    - Musical Youth (Box A-88, Folder 46)
    - Musicians (Box A-88, Folder 47)
      Photographer if identified: Gill Photographers, Raul Melendez, Lloyd Yearwood, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Musicians Ass'd. of Gtr. N.Y. (Box A-88, Folder 48)
      In folder is leaf with "See Aron, Max" written on it.
    - Musick, Jack (Box A-88, Folder 49)
    - Musicus, Milton (Box A-88, Folder 50)
    - Muskie, Edmund (Senator) (Box A-88, Folder 51)
      Note on folder: "(1968 Vice Presidential Candidate)." Also one press release.
      Photographer if identified: Jules Schick, Lurton Berinsky
    - Muslim Rally (Box A-88, Folder 52)
      Photographer if identified: William C4X N.Y., Merrill A. Roberts, Harris Photo, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Muslims (Box A-88, Folder 53)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Merrill A. Roberts Jr., Bro. David McAdams, United Press International, McLain's Photo Service
    - Muslims (Box A-88, Folder 54)
      Photographer if identified: Henry Arvinger, United Press International, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, Bilal Farid
    - Muslims (Box A-88, Folder 55)